<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</title>
    <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eastern.nl - Performance Engineering done with passion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>nl-NL</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acc.eastern.nl/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description> Contact Mobile: +31 6 55 118 025
Email: erik@eastern.nl
Website: http://www.eastern.nl Mailing adresss Balustrade 20
7325 GP Apeldoorn
The Netherlands Other information IBAN: NL40RABO0393346072
KvK: 08132235
VAT: NL002033564B54 Terms and conditions Nederland ICT 2014 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>References</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:05:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/references/</guid>
      <description>Ik heb Erik leren kennen tijdens mijn rol als projectmanager ‘Ontwikkeling werkplek infrastructuur’ bij het VUmc. Erik heeft een belangrijke rol gespeeld in ons skilled testteam, waarbij Erik verantwoordelijk was voor de uitvoering en, bij afwezigheid van de testmanager, de coördinatie van de testen. Erik heeft goede ICT infrastructurele kennis, en weet zijn kennis goed te combineren met collega’s. Erik is praktisch, heeft een gezonde drive voor kwaliteit, kan prioriteiten stellen en staat open voor veranderingen in planningen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>My name is Erik van Oost, living in Apeldoorn – The Netherlands and IT-freelancer since 2003. My passion for IT brings me to places where I work with much enjoyment for organizations who hire me.
I have been working in IT since 2000 and done several functions. In the last 7 years I am specialized in the area of performance testing and engineering. I have gained a lot of experience with developing, programming and analysing performance tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:04:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/pages/services/</guid>
      <description>Performance Test Training Workshop or training how to setup a complete performance test. In this session we will think about the goals of the test, why you want to get the answer of a goal, and how to get answer about a goal.
In a second session we can dive deeper and learn about tooling like JMeter, LoadRunner etc to write a test.
In the end there is a session to include performance testing in a CI/CD pipeline like Jenkins, Github Action, Azure DevOps etc</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VDI Performance Summit</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/vdi-performance-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/vdi-performance-summit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On 29th january I visited the VDI Performance Summit which was organized by LoginVSI. Login VSI provides performance insights for virtualized desktop environments such as Citrix XenApp, XenDesktop, Microsoft RDS and VMware Horizon View.
The summit was, of course, organized around the LoginVSI tool. In this blog post I will tell you the 5 quick takes of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;images/vdi-performance-summit.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/vdi-performance-summit.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href=&#34;images/i-love-a-good-performance.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/i-love-a-good-performance.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clock application with milliseconds</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/clock-application-with-milliseconds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 12:57:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/clock-application-with-milliseconds/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The clock application with milliseconds which run always on top! This little tool is build to capture the exact time in case of an performance problem. With an extra tool for video recording it can help to record the screen of the user, and see the probably performance slowness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/clock.png&#34; alt=&#34;clock picture&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detailed logon information from Citrix Director</title>
      <link>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/detailed-logon-information-from-citrix-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 12:57:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acc.eastern.nl/en/blog/detailed-logon-information-from-citrix-director/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-to-have-detailed-logon-information-from-citrix&#34;&gt;Why to have detailed logon information from Citrix?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes anyone is asking you, the performance is not what we like. Within a Citrix environment it is easy to get into the director to see the overview of the logon times.
By default Citrix Director gives the following information about the logon:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;images/citrix-director.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/citrix-director.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
